<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<Walkthrough xmlns="http://schemas.datacontract.org/2004/07/Demo.Samples" xmlns:i="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" encoding="UTF-8">
   <chapter>
      <title>Prologue</title>
      <content>When the game starts, head to the guard, then aim at the hostages to make them
move into the closet. Bring up your phone to detonate the explosives set by T.
and move through the hall to collect your reward. After the short scene, switch
to T. by holding the down button. Use the right analog stick to switch and kill
the guard with a headshot.

At the end of the hallway, take cover behind some crates. Move outside and a 5-
star Wanted Level is automatically triggered. Kill the cops one by one while
staying behind pillars and objects, then slowly but surely move forward on the
road until you reach the vehicle at the far left side. Drive to the end of the
road, turn right when indicated and shoot as many cops as you can to trigger a
series of scenes and to finish the game's first mission 'successfully'.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Franklin and Lamar</title>
      <content>As Franklin, follow Lamar and choose one of the cars (red or white). Keep
following Lamar by car until he enters a parking lot; simply keep track of the
little blip on your minimap to get an idea of where Lamar is (or is headed).
Be sure not to hit any of the 'aliens' at the movie set, and keep up with Lamar
to fulfill all completion requirements (besides not damaging the car too much,
and using Franklin's special ability for 7 seconds).

Just your luck; the cops show up and you'll have to get rid of a 2-star Wanted
Level. Exit the parking lot and accelerate on the road while also monitoring
your minimap to avoid any incoming police cars. If you can stay out of the
Wanted Zone long enough you'll automatically lose the Wanted Level. When you
have done so, take your car back to the dealer. After the scene, all you have to
do is drive to Franklins home and park the car in his garage to end the mission.

              TROPHY/ACHIEVEMENT UNLOCKED: Welcome to Los Santos
              ¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯¯
You can rest (save your game) in his bedroom. There's a health pack in the
kitchen (as well as beer) and of course you can watch some funny TV shows.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Repossession</title>
      <content>Head over to Simeon's dealership, then follow the waypoint and park the car on
the road. Climb over the fence and follow Lamar to the end of the street. Since
you'll want to finish this mission in a speedy fashion, immediately open up the
garage on the right (which triggers a scene - the other doesn't).

Collect the dropped weapon afterwards and start dispatching the gang members one
by one while staying mostly covered. Keep in mind that if you want a perfect
ranking, you'll have to kill at least six enemies with headshots, and you must
also have a shooting accuracy of 70%+. When the car crashes into the wall, shoot
the gasoline trail, then quickly dispatch any remaining enemies and run back to
your car to chase the biker.

Don't allow for too much distance between you and the biker, or the mission will
automatically fail. If you can catch up with him, try driving next to him and
trigger Franklin's special to enter slow motion; this allows you to get a good
shot at the driver. Alternatively you can also crash your car into him if you're
certain you'll hit him. Grab the bike and drive it back to the indicated carwash
to finish the mission.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Complications</title>
      <content>Head back to Simeon to find out he wants another vehicle. Drive yourself to the
waypoint and climb over the fence. Enter stealth mode (press the left analog
stick) and sneak up on the gardener, then knock him out. Enter the house by
going via the back; climb on the car, then on the roof and go inside the window.

Although the scenes that play when detected are hilarious (especially the one
downstairs), you cannot be seen by any of the residents or it'll be game over.
Head downstairs, turn left and enter the garage to reach the car.

Drive back to Simeon and do as you're told; drive through the glass window of
his shop. After this, defeat Simeon in a hand-to-hand fight. Be sure to never
get hit by him if you want 100% completion for this mission.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Father/Son</title>
      <content>Switch back to Franklin and head over to Michael's house; he's 'waiting' for you
in the backyard. Turns out there's some work to do, so hop in the car and drive
towards the waypoint.

Once you reach it, a truck with the boat on top drives past; quickly chase it!
Move the car close enough so Franklin can climb on top of the vehicle and help
him out by shooting the gang member when he asks for your help. Be sure to catch
Jimmy as soon as possible by driving underneath him; do so within 10 seconds if
you want full completion for this mission. After all this, drive towards the
closest Los Santos Customs (Pay and Spray) to repair your car. Drive Jimmy back to
Michael's house and be sure not to get as much as a scratch on it.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Pulling Favors</title>
      <content>Drive up to the question mark indicated on your minimap. Tonya is one of the
many 'Stranger and Freaks' characters who give out (side) missions. This one's
a mandatory one in order to continue with the main story.

The mission itself is very simple. Drive up to indicated waypoint and get inside
the vehicle. Drive up to the car you're supposed to deliver and hook the crane
onto the car by driving up in front of it; the crane can be lowered by using
the left analog stick. Make your way back to the parking lot and place the
vehicle inside the indicated zone to finish this mission.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title />
      <content />
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Marriage Counseling</title>
      <content>Head back to Michael (as Franklin) and you'll find more (household) trouble.
Follow the car and drive up the tracks as indicated, then stop the car and hook
it up.

As you drive back home, Madrazo's men are on your tail. Switch to Franklin and
kill all three of them. Save the driver for last and quickly head back home to
fully complete this mission.

After this you can pay Dr. Friedlander a visit for a funny scene (although it
does cost you $500 - yeah, sometimes it sucks to live in the capitalistic U.S.).</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title />
      <content />
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Friend Request</title>
      <content>There are several missions you can do at this point, but we have to start
somewhere, so let's meet a new employer called Lester. Remember that you can
turn on navigation by entering the main menu, going over to the map, and click
on any location on the map (in our case the 'L') to turn on a 'quickest-route'
navigation towards your indicated waypoint.

Lester wants you to invade the Lifeinvader building for starters. You'll need to
dress as a geek first, so stop by the Suburban outfitter and purchase a new set
of jeans and shirt. When you're all set to go, head over to the Lifeinvader
office and chill out with the programmer, then follow him to his office. You'll
have to help him get rid of his porn-laden PC first (as if a programmer doesn't
know how to); do this within 32 seconds to get full completion on this mission.

After this, head inside the nearby office marked on your minimap to place the
prototype. Head back home, watch some TV and flick on the right channel where
Lifeinvader CEO Jay Norris is doing a marketing talk. As soon as he pulls out
his smartphone, grab your own, go to contacts and 'call' Jay to finish this
mission.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>The Good Husband</title>
      <content>Once you've done the previous mission and drive around a little, Amanda will
call you saying she's in trouble. If you agree to help her (and as a good
husband, you should) then this mission is automatically accepted. 

Drive over to the police car as indicated on your minimap and hop inside. This
will instantly trigger a 3-star Wanted Level, so you'll want to step on it while
at the same time keeping a close eye on the minimap to avoid any incoming cops.
Avoid them long enough and the stars will begin to blink, until they vanish
completely after a little more time has passed. After this, simply drive Amanda
back home and dump the police car.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Casing the Jewel Store</title>
      <content>Before going back to Lester for the next mission, suit up (that's right, in a
suit, not in casual clothes) at Michael's place. Lester has an idea on how to
make some decent dollars and it involves jewelry.

Drive over to the waypoint and enter the Vangelico jewelry store. Inside, look
to your left and make a photo of the alarm keypad. Next, turn right and take a
photo of the vent. Then search the ceiling nearby (still on the right side) for
the camera and take a picture of that as well. If you get too close to the sales
lady, Michael will be forced into a conversation; it's not harmful, but it does
add to the mission time, which makes it more difficult to get 100%.

Exit the store and drive around the block to find an entrance to the roofs. Go
upstairs and up the two ladders, then move to the far end of the roofs, climbing
another ladder and moving on top of the last roof to find a high vantage point.
From here you can photograph the ventilation system of the jewelry store. Head
back to your vehicle and drive back to Lester's place.

Here you'll set up the first heist of the game. Depending on your approach, a
good gunman supposedly becomes more or less important, as Lester mentions
himself. However, it is worth mentioning that hiring a good gunman *is*
important in this case. A good driver and a good hacker are also important to
have around.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Chop</title>
      <content>As Franklin, drive up to his house to initiate this mission. Follow Lamar into
the van and drive to the waypoint. After the short scene, chase the biker until
he gets off, then give chase by foot. After climbing over several obstacles and
crashing through a fence you'll reach some train tracks, where you'll soon
enough lose the biker.

Change to Chop and stay in his perspective for ten seconds, then switch back to
Franklin again and start opening up the train boxcars. The first two don't hold
anything, but (after Chop goes 'I say what what in the butt') the next train
does. At this point you'll essentially have caught the biker, so carefully drive
back to Franklin's place, then park the car at the nearby parking lot to finish
this mission.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>The Long Stretch</title>
      <content>As Franklin, drive home to activate this mission, which consists of three
phases. The first phase is easiest; simply drive to the indicated waypoint to
purchase a Shotgun (with Flashlight) and some ammunition at Ammu-Nation. It's
a good idea to also purchase some armor. Don't take your time since there's a
time limit on this mission for 100% completion. Drive to the waypoint and enter
the building to trigger a scene.

Of course things go wrong or it wouldn't be much of a mission. Make your way
through the room up ahead by staying behind cover and killing the gang members
with your shotgun. Try to kill as many as you can by aiming for their heads and
prevent getting hit as much as possible if you want a golden ranking. In the
next hall (where Lamar falls to the ground due to an exploding door) look for a
health kit. There is one more health kit at the far end of the big storage room;
it's next to the double doors you're supposed to go through in the corner. Waste
the last few gang members and head outside.

A 3-star Wanted Level is the price you pay for accepting shady offers from
friends. You can try to kill the gunmen from the helicopter although you might
as well make a run for it to the nearby ladder. Follow Stretch and Lamar until
you reach the road; quickly steal a car and escape the cops 'as usual'. You may
find it difficult to escape them at first, but take a good look at your minimap
and step on it. Eventually you'll lose the cops and you can drive back home.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Daddy's Little Girl</title>
      <content>At Michael's place a scene automatically takes place when you return. Drive to
the beach and select one of the bikes. The race is straightforward and there is
no penalty for losing, but you'll want to stay on the bike without falling off
even once to get full completion. When you've reached the end of the race, swim
to the boat as fast as you can (under one minute is required for completion).

When you're racing the Seashark, quickly head for the sewers as indicated on the
minimap and try to reach the top speed. You should be able to lose the celebs
as long as you don't bump into things all the time. Return to the beach to
finish this mission.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Bugstars Equipment</title>
      <content>This is in fact a very easy mission if you do it right. One easy way to get a
Bugstar van is to go to the southmost 'H' (mark it with a waypoint for your
convenience). When you reach the building, head around the right side (instead
of the front side) and enter stealth mode by pressing the left analog stick.
Knock out the man standing behind the van and steal the vehicle; simply drive
back out (not through the front, since there are more employees there) and park
the van near Lester's place.

Note: If one of the employees notices you during the theft, they'll call the
      police and you'll have to shake them off first</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>BZ Gas Grenades</title>
      <content>Pinpoint the second 'H' (heist) setup and follow the van. Be sure to shoot open
the back doors to get 100% completion on this mission, then take the van and
avoid the cops. Drive back to Lester to finish this short mission.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>The Jewel Store Job</title>
      <content>After getting the necessary equipment for the heist, it's on! Drive to the
jewelry store's block, then - as Franklin - head back to the highest vantage
point on the roofs and throw a Gas Grenade into the ventilation system.

After this, steal the jewelry with Michael as quickly as possible. All breakable
cases are indicated with green dots and there are 20 of them in total. Snatch
all of them within 50 seconds for 100% completion.

Back outside, follow your teammates by bike and drive through the sewers. When
you're back outside, keep the cops of your team members by driving into them;
the truck's heavy enough to destroy cop cars easily. You'll soon enough lose the
cops, after which you only have to drive back to the final waypoint.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Mr. Philips</title>
      <content>It's finally time to revisit one of the most insane videogame characters of all
time; Trevor. Drive to the indicated waypoint and a chase begins. Kill the two
bikers by shooting them and keep following the van.

When the van finally stops, a large shootout commences. Take cover and start
killing bikers, preferably with headshots. There are some large gas containers
you can shoot which can help you destroy the area/bikers. When the last few
bikers start fleeing, show no mercy and quickly kill every last one of them
(that is, if you want 100% completion, and you do want that).

Drive up to Ortega's trailer and push it into the river, then kill him and
return to Trevors house after dropping off Ron.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Trevor Philips Industries</title>
      <content>Drive up to the bar indicated by the only mission letter on your map, then drive
your companions to the 'lab'. After more bizarre hilariousness, get ready for a
big shootout. Stay covered and take out the Aztecas one by one. The first wave
can partly be defeated by aiming for the cars while using Trevor's special to
blow them up. 

Follow Chef's instructions and be sure not to get hit to ensure completion.
When Chef offers you a bigger weapon, quickly head back inside and find him on
the other roof. The Grenade Launcher he hands to you is very effective for
distant crowd control, and it also allows you to destroy the required 6 vehicles
for full mission completion. When you get back downstairs, pop another grenade
out the entrance, then be sure to go outside and destroy the vehicles in which
some of Ortega's men are trying to escape to ensure you've reached 32 kills.
To recover any health lost, grab the health kit from the counter.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Nervous Ron</title>
      <content>This is a fairly lengthy mission; first you'll have to collect a Sniper Rifle
from the Ammu-Nation along with a scope and silencer. Drive to the vantage point
afterward. From here, the idea is to cover Ron from any guards. After you kill
the first guard below the watchtower, shoot the lights to prevent the guard in
the jeep from seeing him. Keep taking out guards - preferably at least 5 with
headshots, although those headshots can also be done later - as Ron draws closer
to the gas tanks. Also take out the helicopter pilot when he's settled. After it
has crashed, quickly make your way over to Ron and kill any bikers in your way
(and perform any headshots you still had to make). Beware of the last biker in
the hangar as you enter.

While on the wing of the plane, kill all bikers you see - this is part of the
requirements for mission completion. First aim for the guy on the bike, then
waste the rest in front of you. When you take control of the plane, one of the
bikers clings on to the plane. He'll let go sooner or later, so don't worry
about it.

Flying is new and thus may be tricky. There are six bridges along the flight
path (which essentially means the path that Ron is taking) and if you want this
mission fully completed, you'll have to carefully fly underneath all six of
them. I'd suggest doing this later on a replay. For now, focus on dropping the
cargo near the boats in the sea (but be sure to fly relatively low while near a
military base); simply release the cargo while flying through the blue circle on
your minimap.

After this, the only thing left to do is to head back to the landing strip.
Winning the race against Ron isn't hard, but landing can indeed be tricky,
especially if you've never done it before. Try to align the plane correctly as
you start to approach the landing strip; this is the most important part and you
can't make major adjustments when you're about to land or you'll tear the plane
apart. Focus on the landing strip with B (Xbox 360) or Circle (PS3). Stop
accelerating and slowly lose some altitude. The landing gear can be extended by
pressing the left analog stick.

                         PROPERTIES CAN NOW BE BOUGHT</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Crystal Maze</title>
      <content>Cheng's got more work for you - or has he? After meeting up, drive to O'Neil
brother's farm and approach the vantage point by foot. You'll want to start
taking out enemies with headshots as soon as possible, but also pay attention to
your accuracy if you're going for perfection.

Inside the farm, take cover and turn left, then immediately take out the guys
in the adjacent rooms. You can find a health kit in the nearby restroom, and
there's one more in the living room - to your immediate left as you enter.
These should keep you going as you make your way downstairs from that same
living room. Kill the last guy here and grab the gasoline tank. Pour gasoline
along the indicated line and shoot it once outside. Simply back away from the
farm to complete this mission. Whassup, Cheng?</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Friends Reunited</title>
      <content>Go to Trevor's house to start this mission. Drive to the trailer park and take
out your sniper rifle; shoot the first guard straight ahead (and make it a
headshot). The idea is quite simple: plant the sticky bombs at the indicated
trailers without being detected (you can still finish the mission when you're
detected, but 100% completion is out of reach). Two bikers will soon make their
way off; if you want to you can ignore them, but shooting them through the head
allows for a perfect score.

There are two other bikers standing still down the road to the right/east side
of the trailer park that you'll also want to take out with headshots. Then
there's the arguing couple nearby the trailer in the middle; take out the guy
with a headshot as well.

Once you've placed all sticky bombs, destroy all trailers all at once. After
this you'll only have to make your way to Los Santos with a short scenery stop
on the way.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Fame or Shame</title>
      <content>As Trevor, drive to Michael's place for a happy reunion... or something like it,
anyway. Make your way to the Fame and Shame studio to watch a scene. After this,
chase Lazlow outside and get in the huge Phantom truck.

A chase begins; don't worry about having to knock Lazlow off the road - that's
not going to happen. Instead try keeping the trailer hooked while also stepping
on it to get the maximum speed out of this beast. Staying close to Lazlow is
also an important part of 100% completion.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Dead Man Walking</title>
      <content>Drive over to the FIB to have a little chat with Dave. Some mysteries are
unraveled and you're forced to do a mission for him.. After waking up from a
body bag, sneak behind the nearby FIB agent and knock him out. Just so you know,
this isn't a sneaking mission, so you can take out any other enemies beyond this
point by simply shooting them (preferably with headshots). First check the two
bodies in the other room, then start making your way through the hall up ahead,
taking out FIB agents as you go. There's a health kit on the counter if you
need it.

Head upstairs and clear out the room ahead. There's another health kit in the
storage room, as well as a window which is your way out of the building. Snatch
a decent car (one of the parked ones should suffice) and make your way out of
here; you've got a 3-star Wanted Level you'll need to escape. After you've done
so, meet up with Franklin to finish this mission.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Did Somebody Say Yoga?</title>
      <content>As Michael, drive back home to start this mission. The start is fairly strange
for a mission; you'll have to perform three sets of yoga moves. These are very
simple to perform, and the analog sticks arrows will light up green when they're
in the right position. At this point all you need to do is hold them that way,
hold down LT/RT or L2/R2, and release those triggers again after Michael's air
gauge has filled up completely, all while holding the analogs sticks still in
the indicated direction.

After successfully performing the yoga poses (or not), quickly go to Jimmy's 
room and drive to the indicated waypoint as soon as possible, then back to
Michael's house again. You'll find that driving soon becomes more and more
difficult. What's going on? One of the weirdest scenes in the game plays, and
you're out on the street again afterwards. Quickly snatch a car and drive home,
since there's a time limit on this mission for completion.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Three's Company</title>
      <content>As Michael, drive up to the FIB headquarters to meet up with Dave. After the
scene, quickly drive to the indicated waypoint to meet up with Trevor and
Franklin.

Your goal now is to fly the chopper to one of the highest buildings in town, as
indicated on your minimap. When you hover over the right spot (but don't fly
too high above it), Michael will be able to automatically drop himself. Descend
by jumping until you reach the interrogation room.

At this point it's a good idea to switch to Franklin and start wasting agents;
remember you'll need 10 headshots for mission completion, but also 60%+
accuracy. When the game tells you to, immediately switch to Michael and finish
off the remaining agents (and now's your time to get any remaining headshots).

When you've done so, switch back to Franklin to deal with the first chopper;
kill the pilot with a headshot whenever you get him steady in your scope. Switch
to Michael after this and gun down the three remaining choppers, but be careful;
you'll want to keep your accuracy up, so shoot in controlled bursts and only
when the crosshair's aimed directly at one of your opponents. Defeat them and
the mission's a success.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Hood Safari</title>
      <content>Head over to Franklin's house where both Lamar and Trevor show up. After the
scene, get inside the van and drive to the place where the 'thing' is happening.
Things quickly go bad and a big shootout commences. Stay behind walls and cars
while you push through the street. As usual, try to focus on headshots and
accuracy for completion.

When the cops show up, press through the alley to the far left side of the
street until you reach a sewer canal. Climb on one of the jet ski's and follow
Lamar. Soon enough you'll split ways; at this point all you have to do is lose
the cops. One way to do this is to simply keep going over the water near the
coast. The chopper sooner or later gives up. Stay out of sight from any police
boats and you'll be fine.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>By the Book</title>
      <content>Switch back to Trevor and you'll soon get a call from Michael. If you switch to
Michael at this point, Trevor will automatically meet him. After the scene,
drive to the first target. You'll have to torture Mr. K. afterward. In order to
fully complete this mission, all you need to do is make sure he never gets a
heart attack, and you'll have to perform all four possible torture methods on
him. Simply don't torture him too long and scare him to fulfill the necessary
requirements.

Meanwhile, as Michael, you're first going to have to drive towards the target's
house. Then, as you get more and more clues, search for a bearded man smoking
a lot with his left hand. He should be on the lower level near the TV. After 
this, all you need to do is drive Mr. K to the airport to finish this mission.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Scouting the Port</title>
      <content>Head back to "Trevor's" safehouse to initiate this mission. Drive to the docks
and follow Floyd to the container handler. You're supposed to grab the two
containers standing at the other side of the area by moving the handler to their
(long) side and picking them up (one at a time). Once the handler has been
positioned correctly, lower it and attach the container with the right button.
Move the container up a bit with the left analog stick and move it to the
designated area, then lower it again with the left analog and detach it; do the
same for the second container.

Climb up the nearby crane (indicated on your minimap) and enter the cabin by
climbing the ladder down near your colleague. The goal here is to position the
crane directly above the containers. You can switch viewpoints by pressing
BACK/SELECT, and the right analog stick moves the crane left/right and up/back.
Once you've attached a container, hoist it up and move the crane to the other
end of the containers - the right side, where you can drop it off on the truck.
Do the same for the second container.

You'll now have to photograph the front of the ship, a guard (there's one in the
middle of the ship) and the back of the ship respectively and send these photos
to Ron. Climb back down and drive the truck to the waypoint. Be sure you do not
lose the container or the mission will fail; in other words, drive safely! A
scene triggers when you reach the waypoint. Simply make a run for it and return
to the safehouse.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Hotel Assassination</title>
      <content>As Franklin, drive over to Lester who's got an opportunity for him. The deal's
simple: You have to assassinate some big guy and you get a nice reward in terms
of cash.

Drive over to the waypoint, which is at the lowest floor of a parking lot, and
move a little to the right side of the parking lot. Grab out your sniper rifle
and wait for the target to come out of the hotel. He's very easy to spot, but
if you must know, he's got a pink shirt and is escorted by two guards. Kill him
and leave the area to complete this mission. Easy as pie!</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>The Multi Target Assassination</title>
      <content>This is another mission for Franklin. Pick up the phone (oldschool GTA style) as
indicated by 'L' to start this multi-assassination mission, which is a lot
harder than the previous one. You'll need to kill the following four targets:

1. A bodybuilder juror near the beach.
2. A juror on a sailboat.
3. A window cleaner juror (attached high up to a building).
4. A juror on a bike.

You have considerably less time compared to the previous mission, and if you
want 100% completion you'll have to step on it and kill them one after another
as quickly as possible.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Minisub</title>
      <content>This is a very easy mission, but for 100% completion you do have to know what
you're doing. Locate the submarine and you'll notice it's hanging from a large
freighter. Don't board the boat; instead move to the right side and look for a
long ladder leading you to a good high vantage point. Grab out your sniper rifle
and shoot off the cables at the pulleys to make the sub drop in the water.

Quickly climb back down and run around the freighter, dive in the water around
the right side, climb on top of the sub and enter. Now all you need to do is
steer it all the way to the indicated waypoint; however, directions may be
confusing at this point, and there are some harbors up ahead that take extra
time if you end up sailing into those. It's a good idea to bring up your main
menu map and see where you're supposed to go, saving yourself any detours.

The last and final part of this mission consists of driving the truck with the
sub loaded onto it to a safe spot.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Tow Truck</title>
      <content>For now, this walkthrough will continue with a series of FIB related missions,
but feel free to skip ahead to a mission you'd like to do instead.

Head over to the 'B' for another FIB mission. There are four FIB-related heist
locations you can now go to. Let's start with the one on the southwest part of
town; this is a simply pick-up-a-truck-and-deliver-it-back mission. Knock out
the man working on his car (so he can't complain about you stealing his truck,
but more importantly so that you don't get any Wanted Level) and quickly drive
the truck back to the FIB lot.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Trash Truck</title>
      <content>This FIB-related heist location is on the east/northeast of town and pinpoints
a trash truck. Unfortunately stealing it triggers a 2-star Wanted Level which
you'll have to get rid of. One way to do this is to drive off a hill into the
highway, where you can strategically wait until the Wanted Level wears off. If
you can also keep the truck undamaged, this should be enough for completion.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Boiler Suits</title>
      <content>The easiest mission in the game, this simply requires you to go to the Ammu-
Nation in the middle of town (also indicated with a Heist icon) and purchase
three (different colored) boiler suits. Do this within 30 seconds and leave the
store to get 100% mission completion.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Masks</title>
      <content>The last part of the FIB heist setup series (besides getting a getaway vehicle,
which is easy - it's not too relevant where you place it) requires you to
purchase three masks. For 100% completion, you'll have to purchase the masks
within 20 seconds and the masks have to be white hockey masks.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>The Merryweather Heist</title>
      <content>Visit Trevor's safehouse (for example as Michael) to start this heist. You'll
first have to drive Franklin into position. After this, take out the two guys on
the freighter with headshots.

As Michael, sneak around the ship while you plant the bombs at the indicated
spots. This isn't too hard, but you'll want to avoid being seen. Take out any
enemies as soon as possible, preferably with headshots to save Franklin as much
trouble as you can. After setting the first three bombs, move to the ship's
stern entrance and go upstairs. Michael will take care of the last bomb by
himself.

As Franklin you'll now have to snipe a great deal of enemies, including a pilot
chopper. Aim for their heads as much as possible and keep track of how many
headshots you still need (out of 12) for 100% completion, then take out the
enemies regularly when you've reached that amount.

Quick dive towards the device as soon as you gain control of Michael. When he's
located it, all you have to do is get Trevor to fetch it with the sub. Hover
over the blip (check your minimap) and lower the submarine to attach it, then
make your way to the other side of the docks to finish this mission.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Blitz Play</title>
      <content>When you've done all the FIB heist preparations, meet back at the original
meeting place to start this mission (indicated by 'H'). You'll first have to
block the road with the garbage truck, which is easy. Ram the security truck,
then plant a sticky bomb at the back.

A *lot* of cops show up afterwards and a 4-star Wanted Level is automatically
gained. At this point, take cover with Franklin behind the road blocks and start
taking out police officers. When the game tells you to switch characters it's
always a good idea to do so. Michael's position is a little higher than
Franklin's and he has a good overview of a large part of the street, including
the back alley.

Trevor on the other hand has a long distant vantage point. The game will tell
you to switch to him when snipers on the roof to the right side (across the
street) are shooting at Michael and Franklin, and he'll also need to take out
the chopper. Be sure to switch regularly (and at least ten times).

When the cops have finally been thinned out, get in the garbage truck as
Franklin and drive to your getaway vehicle, then destroy the truck. The mission
is as good as complete now. As Michael, simply drive towards a new contact to
finish things.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Mr. Richards</title>
      <content>As Michael, drive over to 'S', that is - Solomon the famous movie director. He's
got a little problem he could use your help with. First of all, drive to the
waypoint and climb over the fence. Sneak to the ladder on the left side of the
two workers and make your way over the roofs, sneaking behind workers and
knocking them out before the get a chance to alarm anyone else.

At the top, give Rocco a beating, then get inside the helicopter. You'll have 
scare the movie star, which isn't too hard. Simply ascend as far as you can,
then quickly descend (but without hitting anything). Do this a couple of times,
then return to the studio. Landing might be a little tricky, especially if you
don't want to damage the Frogger at all, so take your time and slowly hold it
steady as you lower it. Make your way back to Solomon to finish the mission.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>I Fought the Law..</title>
      <content>Meet Devin to get this mission, which is fairly straightforward. As Franklin
you'll have to drive towards the waypoint at a gas station where you're supposed
to race two youngsters in speedy cars. The race itself isn't too hard, but you
will have to step up that pedal to keep up, since their cars are very fast.
Be sure to drive between the two trucks and buses as well for completion
purposes, and you might as well use Franklin's special ability during those
times.

After racing for a while you'll shift to police officers Michael and Trevor.
The race now basically pursues by bike. Be sure to follow Trevor through the
tunnel for completion purposes. Other than that, the race is easy. After the
scene, quickly head back to town to finish the mission timely.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Eye in the Sky</title>
      <content>Meet up with Devin (as either Franklin or Trevor) to activate this mission.
During the first part you'll be using Trevor's LSPD chopper to see if you can
spot the right target. Eavesdrop on three conversations while you're at it.
When you've located the target, keep following him and when he gets in the
Z-Type, keep on doing what you're doing.

The Z-Type will enter a building soon. Turn on heat sensors and spot the guy
sitting in a car to the far left, who's somewhat nervously looking around;
that's your target. As Franklin, pop him (otherwise you'll have to deal with a
2-star Wanted Level) and deliver the Z-Type back to Devin; ride easy and take
no damage for 100% completion!</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Caida Libre</title>
      <content>Visit your old friend Martin Madrazo (with either Michael or Trevor) to start
this mission. As Michael, drive to the van with the special gun. You'll have to
shoot the airplane three times, but you can't just aim at it directly and
expect to hit it; the distance is too long. You'll have to shoot in the red
square instead; do this correctly three times and the plane will crash. It's
much easier to shoot the square when the plane is still coming at you in the
far distance right at the beginning, so try taking it out during that time.

When the plane crashes, follow it with Trevor on the Sanchez bike. Don't fall
off and speed up to reach top speed and do the mission under the given time
limit for 100% completion. When you've retrieved the files, all you need to do
is get the van away from the observatory and destroy it. Afterwards, drive back
to Trevor to find out what's going on.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>The Vice Assassination</title>
      <content>Another classic assassination mission, and a very easy one at that. Drive to the
waypoint, get out of the vehicle across the road and run up the hill so you can
see the hooker through your sniper rifle's scope. Wait for a guy in a car with
an open roof to drive up and immediately shoot him in the head as soon as the
hooker enters his car. Quickly get in your car and leave the area.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Deep Inside</title>
      <content>Meet Devin with Franklin to steal another exclusive car. You'll have to sneak
into the movie studio and knock the actor out cold stealthily. Snatch the car
(indicated by the dot) and as you exit the studio, drive over the actor again.

Unfortunately one of the actresses is still in the car and she'll make handling
the vehicle more difficult than it normally is. To make matters worse, security
from the studio will be following you. Fortunately you soon discover that this
car has the special ability to drop spikes, allowing you to shake off your
pursuers. Not too long after that the ejector button becomes available. Quickly
give it a try, will you?

Since there's no time limit on this mission, now's a good time to try and reach
the top speed on the JB 700. Just do it safely, please. You'll want to deliver
the car in perfect shape, remember?</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>The Bus Assassination</title>
      <content>This is another fairly simply assassination job. After getting the call from
Lester, drive to the bus and present yourself as busdriver as you make a few
stops. Your target will soon enter. It's much easier to kill him by simply
shooting him, although driving him over after he gets on his bike will count
towards completion. Escape the 2-star Wanted Level afterwards to finish this
mission.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Minor Turbulence</title>
      <content>As Franklin, drive over to 'M' (Michael's place), to do a mission with *Trevor*.
Yeah, strange setup, but that's how it is. With Trevor, drive to the airplane
and fly it to the big jet while staying low to the ground so you stay
undetected; there's really not much more to it than that. When you get close
enough, gain some altitude and crash into the back of the jet. They'll shoot
some RPG's at you as you approach, but that shouldn't be much of a problem.

Inside, kill everyone including the pilot and steer the jet back to the
indicated waypoint.. except that things go slightly different. To 'shake off'
the F-16's, gain some altitude. They will engage nonetheless, so you'll have to
leave the plane. You can in fact do this by getting into the car in the cargo
room (which is part of this mission's 100% completion), but alternatively you
can just jump out the plane regularly. Yep, perfectly normal, jumping out of
planes.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Paleto Score Setup</title>
      <content>Drive over to the 'B' to progress with the main story. You'll first have to
drive to the bus and pick up Lester. From here, drive to the bank, which isn't
far away. Drive around the other side and shoot the alarm (focus on it to better
spot the red-shaped alarm attached to the wall). Drive up to the nearby gas
station to see what the response rate is. After this it's only a matter of
racing Michael back to the meth lab. If you don't do anything stupid (and
especially watch the wild curves after exiting the tunnel) you should be fine;
the bike's more than fast enough.

It is here that you'll choose a gunman for your next heist. Chef's a good one;
in any case, don't take the worst.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Military Hardware</title>
      <content>To prepare for the upcoming heist you'll need some military hardware. Getting
this isn't too easy, but with the right strategy it's far from hard. Get a
decent car and close in on the 'H' military convoy. When you're just a little
beyond the nearby crossroads, park the car in the middle of the left lane and
back away slightly; let the convoy get a little closer. Alternatively you'll
want to plant a sticky bomb a little further down the road and stop the convoy
with that.

Either way, shoot the driver of the military truck in the head and do the same
with as many other soldiers as you can. Quickly take cover behind your own car
as soon as they start shooting at you. Remember that you can use Trevor's
special which also reduces incurred damage. With the soldiers out of the way,
all that's left to do now is to get in the military truck and park it in the
indicated space a little further down the road.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Predator</title>
      <content>Visit Trevor's place to do this mission. Get in the truck and the scene soon
shifts to Franklin, who's chasing the guys trying to take revenge on Trevor.
After a short chase, walk to the vehicle and the scene shifts back to Trevor.

Fly the chopper to the designated point and Michael will get out a sniper rifle.
Toggle between regular vision and night vision by tapping the right button. Try
to kill the hillbillies with a headshot and don't shoot any wildlife if you want
100% completion on this mission. One of the guys is swimming in the creek to the
left of the forest, the second is walking somewhere in the forest, usually more
on the right side.

The game switches back to Franklin who now has to get the final guy. When you
reach him, quickly grab out your sniper rifle and shoot him in the head. Land
the chopper and go back to the helipad to complete the mission.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>The Paleto Score</title>
      <content>Drive to Trevor's place to finally pull off this heist. Drive towards the bank
and drop Franklin off on the way. When you reach the bank in the van, head
inside and kick the door in. The real action starts when you go back outside...

Looks like that military equipment was good for something after all! Destroy all
vehicles (and officers) to press straight onward and keep expanding the trail
of destruction as the military arrives. You may want to pay attention to your
accuracy, but other than that there are no restrictions.

Soon you'll switch back to Trevor who has acquired not the fastest, but
certainly one of the sturdiest vehicles in the game, a bulldozer. Make your way
to the team so they can get piggyback along. When the tank arrives, quickly
head for the building across the street.

Inside the building it's just a matter of pushing forward. The suits can take a
lot of damage and you should be quick enough to kill most soldiers before they
can shoot at you anyway. At the end, hold off the soldiers long enough until a
train shows up; catch it to beat this mission.

TIP: Now that you have gained some serious cash, it's a good idea to purchase
¯¯¯¯ all available weapons and weapon upgrades, along with a healthy stock of
     ammunition. It's also a good idea to purchase a heavy armor before every
     mission - you'll last much longer that way, and you can easily afford it!
     Be sure to switch to the better weapon types in your weapon wheel after
     purchasing them (use the directional pad).</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Derailed</title>
      <content>Go back to Trevor's to do this mission. Get on the bike with Trevor and chase
the train. You'll need to jump on top of it with the bike, which can be fairly
tricky; drive besides it on the elevated path and when you see an opportunity to
stunt on top of it, do so. If you manage to do so on the first jump it'll count
for completion - good for you. Now drive to the front and Trevor will
automatically get inside.

As Michael, sail to the bridge and move close to the orange container. Select a
sticky bomb throw it at the doors and back away, then blow it open. You'll need
to keep the Merryweather security forces off Michael as he salvages the loot.
After deal with the security guys on the boats and choppers, grab out your
sniper rifle and switch to thermal vision to take out the four snipers on top of
the bridge (one of them is in the far back). Switch back to your assault rifle
afterwards as another chopper is incoming, along with a few paratroopers.

When they have all been killed, get on the boat. Naturally there will be
pursuers both on the water and land. Try to shoot the *guys* on the boats
instead of the boats themselves; it's more effective. Get rid of the jeeps and
the chopper and you're all clear to smoothly sail to the waypoint at the beach
up ahead.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Monkey Business</title>
      <content>It's best to switch to Franklin since he should be close to the starting point
(very close in fact, while Trevor is all the way on the other side of the
island) of this mission.

Sail the boat to the waypoint and dive into the water. Dive towards the grid and
cut it loose. Hold the cutting tool at the green dots and then cut away for
about a secondly you'll hear a metal clunk sound when you've fully cut a spot.
Swim to the far end of the tunnel and get out of the water.

Our James Bond-esque mission continues as our (anti)heroes sneak further into
the facility. Take out the scientists by using your stun gun. When you've
retrieved the gas, switch to your assault rifle (yeah, no problem, all your guns
were in that diving suit, between your legs). As you press onward through the
halls, keep taking cover on one side of the wall and shoot any enemies from
there, preferably in the head - you know the drill by now. In the final hall,
right after the double doors near the monkeys is shot open, hide behind the box
immediately around the corner and clear the way first.

When you're finally back outside, have Trevor align the chopper above the
container - carefully. Fly to the waypoint and drop the container on the truck.
After this, all you have to do is drive Trevor to the waypoint and you'll see
for yourself what happens.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Hang Ten</title>
      <content>This is one of the shortest and easiest missions in the game. As Trevor, go back
to 'your' hideout to start this mission. Afterwards, simply drive (relatively
quickly) to the stripclub. Do so within four minutes for 100% completion.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Surveying the Score</title>
      <content>Make you way to Trevor's newly acquired stripclub to start this mission. After
that, drive to the Union Depository and visit the two important entrances of
the bank. After that, (as Trevor), drive to the chopper and fly to the city.

You'll soon spot the convoy; the goal is to keep track of them (which doesn't
necessarily have to be in focus mode - that's only a visual aid) while keeping
the right distance (not too close, not too far away). There are a couple crazy
completionist requirements that are best done on a replay of this mission, since
they require some skill at flying the chopper.

The convoy will soon enough drive through a tunnel; it's a straight one so
simply follow the road until you spot them again at the other side. As soon as
they've entered the Union Depository, quickly go around the (white/red)
building and hover above the construction site so Lester can shoot some video
material. After this, simply switch back to Michael and drive Franklin back to
his home to finish up.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Bury the Hatchet</title>
      <content>As Michael, drive to his home to start this main storyline mission. After the
scene, drive to the airport and you'll fly to another state with a whole new
map - it's not as large as Los Santos obviously, but clearly a lot of work went
into it nonetheless.

Drive to the graveyard to meet up with Trevor. Unfortunately for Michael, a
firefight with Cheng's men will take place after this. Taking cover behind one
of the tombstones near the steps is a good idea; you have a great vantage point
with good overview and it should allow you to clear the first few waves of
enemies. When they've been thinned out, press onward until you finally reach
your car. Kill your opponents with headshots if you're aiming for 100%
completion, but mind your accuracy.

After this, fly the plane back to the airstrip and gently land it. Remember to
eject the landing gear by pressing the left analog stick, and start your descent
early.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Pack Man</title>
      <content>As Franklin, drive over to Devin to get ready and deliver the stolen vehicles.
Once you've put the last car on the truck, you're in for a long, *long* drive.
After about covering about 75% of the distance, cops will be on you. Franklin
will get in the JB 700 to help lose them; remember that this car has built in
guns and can even drop spikes (press the left analog stick for the latter).
With these measures you should be able to shake off the cops. Meet Molly at the
waypoint and the mission's all done.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Fresh Meat</title>
      <content>Head back to Franklin's old house - unfortunately, coming from the previous
mission, there's not exactly a fast way to get there. Steal a fast car and you
can be there in about five real-life minutes, which isn't that bad actually.

Michael's being held by Cheng's men. Select the app Lester gives you (bottom
right of your phone) to track him. Next to the garage doors where the blip on
your radar takes you is a ladder; climb it to reach a courtyard. Take out the
men and head inside to start a major shootout. Push onward and you'll soon
reach Michael - toss him and gun and continue the slaughter.

The last part of this mission simply requires you to get back to Michael's
house. It's not *that* easy, though, as you're constantly pursued. Be quick and
you'll soon enough reach Michael's place, at which point you no longer have to
worry about your pursuers.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>The Ballad of Rocco</title>
      <content>Visit Solomon as Michael and you'll activate this mission. Quickly get in the
nearby car and race after Rocco. Try to shoot at them as you catch up; if you
can manage to ram their car (several times) they may get out. Either shoot them
or drive over 'em, then return to the studio to finish this mission.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Cleaning out the Bureau</title>
      <content>Head over to Lester's factory; after the scene, drive up to the waypoint and
inspect all license plates. When the janitor drive out, follow him from a
distance of, say, ten meters (yeah, the metric system - every sane person on
earth uses that, get over it). Follow him into his apartment on the 1st floor,
go inside and leave after the scene. Drive back to Lester's place to finish the
mission.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Reuniting the Family</title>
      <content>As Michael, head home to start this mission. It's a straightforward A to B
mission: First, drive to Amanda to trigger a scene. Second, drive up to the
tattoo shop and do some 'creative work' there. Head to Friendlander's officer
afterwards, and finally, drive back to home.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Architect's Plans</title>
      <content>Meet up with Lester to get the details of this mission. It's straightforward,
once you've reached the construction site with Franklin, stealthily follow the
architect by going around the right side of the construction area. Watch out for
the pit and sneak back to the main road in the middle of the construction area
to avoid being seen by the two workers.

Ride the elevator up and wait for the architect to converse with the workers,
then follow him inside and knock him out from behind; grab the suitcase and
quickly leave the construction site. If you have a Wanted Level, escape the cops
and return to Lester afterwards.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Doting Dad</title>
      <content>After the previous mission, drive around as Michael and you'll soon get a call
from Tracey who is being stalked. The mission is very simple: Pick Tracey up
and drive around in her car looking for the guy who's got the hots for her, then
when you've located him, waste him and drive back home.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Fire Truck</title>
      <content>You'll soon get a text from Lester who reminds you that a fire truck is
required for the heist (if you chose option A, that is). Call 911 and steal the
fire truck after it arrives; escape the cops and drive it back to Lester's
factory.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Legal Trouble</title>
      <content>As Michael, get back to Solomon to start this mission. Pursue Molly until the
cops add some flavor to the mission. The craziness starts at the airport, so be
sure to watch the Weazel News camera for 15 seconds before all that.

After the first police car smashes into a gas truck, watch out for the other one
that will be swept off its wheels by a plane; don't crash into it! Keep your
distance as Molly destroys half the airport and she'll soon enough crash into a
wall. Follow her inside and collect the film reel. You'll now have to lose the
3-star Wanted Level. One easy way to do it is to get into the nearby plane and
quickly fly away. As far as mission completion goes, that should cover it,
although you might have to lose the cops again if you choose to land on the
same airport. You could also land it at Trevor's airstrip if you wish.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>The Construction Assassination</title>
      <content>It's true, this mission could've been done a while ago, but now you've got a
little break from the stream of main storyline missions, plus you have more than
enough cash to purchase some heavy armor and great set of weapons from Ammu-
Nation (including RPG's). Head over to the construction site and kill all the
body guards both outside as well as inside the building. When you reach the
roof, your target will attempt to escape by helicopter. Grab out your RPG and
fire slightly in front of the chopper (in the direction it's flying) to waste
him. Kill any remaining bodyguards and look for the parachute, then jump off
the building with your chute.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>The Bureau Raid</title>
      <content>Visit Lester's factory to start this mission. As Michael, drive to the FIB
building and go inside. Ride the elevator up and start mopping the floor. You
can clean the dirty spots (indicated with dots on your minimap) by pressing A
(or X on PS3) and clean the mop with LB (or L1 on PS3). The mop can clean two
dirty spots, then it needs to be washed.

Plant the explosive in the locker and move into the next hall. Clean the floor
here and plant the second explosive in the restroom. Exit the building after
doing so.

As Franklin, drive up to the FIB building and head inside. Once you're all the
way upstairs, blow out the doors to get the containment drive by using a sticky
bomb. Remember that you can detonate these by pressing left. After this, make
your way through the building, and as Franklin, kill any FIB agents in your way.
When you're reunited, abseil down the elevator shaft as quickly as possible.
Exit the building and drive to your getaway vehicle. Destroy the fire truck</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>The Wrap Up</title>
      <content>Soon after the last mission, Dave calls you. Meet him to trigger a scene in
which things go horribly wrong and - obviously - leaving you in the middle of a
large firefight. Press onward as you kill your opponents, preferably with
headshots for completion purposes. When you reach the court, Trevor shows up
and helps you out; ideally kill enemies with headshots again while sniping.
Continue as Michael and protect Dave from any crossfire, then switch to Trevor
and waste a couple more enemies.

When you drive away as Michael, a chopper pursues. Grab out a decent weapon and
gun it down - this is part of 100% mission completion anyway. Drive to the
waypoint to meet Trevor again.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Lamar Down</title>
      <content>As Franklin, visit your home to trigger this mission. Drive up to the place
where Lamar is being held and split up your characters to three designated
vantage points. It doesn't matter too much where you put them, as you can switch
between them anyway.

A major shootout starts, so take cover as Franklin when you close in on Lamar's
location, and preferably use headshots. Use your sniper rifle with Michael to
rack up some more headshots. Whenever a character is in trouble, quickly switch
over to them so you can kill any incoming gang members.

When you've reached Lamar and going back to the cars with him, some enemies will
engage Michael, so be quick to switch over and waste them. When you've finally
reached the car again, drive Lamar home to end this mission.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Meltdown</title>
      <content>As soon as you arrive at the indicated starting position (for Michael), purchase
a suit and you'll be driven to the movie. Devin shows up and tells you something
you're not going to be pleased with hearing. Quickly drive to your home and step
on it. Inside, kill the two Merryweather security guys with a headshot, then
head downstairs and sweep the house clear. Push through the garden, staying
covered at all times, then move closer to the front yard and more Merryweather
security shows up. Pulling out your grenade launcher and blasting their jeep
works wonders; shoot any stragglers with your assault rifle and go back upstairs
to finish this mission.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Stingers</title>
      <content>Get to Trevor's stripclub to start preparing for the biggest heist ever.
Depending on which path you choose you'll get different missions. For now, this
guide follows path A; the other path will be implemented soon. It is advisable
to get some good people working on this heist.

You're going to need a Police Transporter (a van), which isn't the easiest
vehicle to steal. The heist location not too far from the stipclub marks one.
Walk past the main entrance and past the police officers, climb over the fence
(the police will turn hostile from this point on), punch the officer coming out
of the building and get in the van.

You'll now have to lose a 3-star Wanted Level, which can be tricky. One way to
do it is to drive into the sewer tunnels. Either way, once you've lost the cops,
park it at the waypoint to complete this mission.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Gauntlet - Pillbox Hill</title>
      <content>One of three pickup missions, you're required to pick up this Gauntlet car at
Pillbox Hill, modify it for the heist and bring it to the indicated garage.
Check your email (on your smartphone) to find the car's position on the map,
along with a photograph.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Gauntlet - Rockford Hills</title>
      <content>One of three pickup missions, you're required to pick up this Gauntlet car at
Rockford Hills, modify it for the heist and bring it to the indicated garage.
Check your email (on your smartphone) to find the car's position on the map,
along with a photograph.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>Gauntlet - Mission Row</title>
      <content>One of three pickup missions, you're required to pick up this Gauntlet car at
Mission Row, modify it for the heist and bring it to the indicated garage.
Check your email (on your smartphone) to find the car's position on the map,
along with a photograph.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>The Big One</title>
      <content>Needless to say, purchase heavy armor and good guns before attempting this.

Head over to Trevor's place to start this mission, the biggest heist ever
pulled. Drive the van to the indicated waypoint in the tunnel and drop the
stinger with the right button, then move away slightly from it. Aim at the
guards as the exit their vehicles, but don't shoot them. 

After entering the vehicle, drive to the Union Depository and get the gold from
the safe. Drive away afterwards until the scene shifts to Franklin. He's in
charge of getting the team safe around town by manipulating the traffic lights.
Keep the lights green for Michael and co. while you keep the lights red for
Merryweather. There's one exception; when your team reaches the lower left
corner of the screen, turn the lights green for the nearby (moving away)
Merryweather so they won't see Michael's team. In turn, stop your own team if
required at this point.

A scene will play after which a massive shootout takes place. Stay behind cover
and switch characters if the game tells you to. It helps quite a bit to take out
any incoming jeeps with the grenade launcher; the explosion will take out
multiple enemies at once. Other than that, use your assault rifle and try to
get at least 20 headshots while keeping your accuracy high as well.

When you've cleared out the area, get inside the cars. You'll have a 5-star
Wanted Level, so step on it and follow your teammates. When you reach the
tunnel, drive into the right truck; the time frame for this is fairly short so
you'll have two attempts at most. Do this successfully and you'll have escaped
the cops. All you have to do now is drive back to Michael's home.</content>
   </chapter>
   <chapter>
      <title>The Third Way</title>
      <content>It is highly advisable to purchase some heavy armor before doing this mission.
The grenade launcher with plenty of ammunition is also invaluable.

You have three options here, but for now this guide is going to take the hard
route; the other two will be added tomorrow. Drive to Lester's place to discuss
the situation, then head to Franklin's old house to pick up Lamar. Drive to
the indicated factory afterwards and head inside to watch a scene.

Shit is about to hit the fan; both Merryweather and the FIB will be searching
the place any minute. Start taking them out one by one and switch characters
whenever required. When Lamar calls for Franklin's help, go upstairs and move to
the far end of the walkway, turn left and go outside. Quickly start taking out
more enemies and use your grenade launcher to take out vehicles. After clearing
out the area in front (near Lamar), switch back to Michael and clear the area,
then move to Trevor.

Head outside (together with Trevor) and take out another wave of enemies, using
any means necessary. Especially watch out for any enemies climbing up the
ladder of the walkway if you decide to stay there for the moment. Be sure to
make use of the holy grenade launcher to wipe out any vehicles including the
incoming chopper(s). When you've dealt with the last few enemies, all that's
left to do now are the following things:

1. Kill Cheng with Franklin. You can use sticky bombs to take out his vehicle.
   Quickly pull out the grenade launcher to destroy the other two vehicles and
   you should be able to escape without any Wanted Level whatsoever.

2. Waste Stretch with Michael. Don't get too close to his parked vehicle;
   instead, get out of your car in the main street, pull out the grenade
   launcher and pop him. Quickly escape the area by car, as his homies are
   eager to gun you down. If you're aiming for 100% completion, however, you'll
   have to take out Stretch with a melee attack.

3. Murder Steve Haines with Trevor. Steve's in the moving Ferris wheel and thus
   may be a little difficult to hit. Move to the left side (on which the wheel
   is coming down) to get a better angle and shoot him in the head when you the
   chance. Quickly get in your vehicle and escape the area from the cops.

4. Kidnap Devin from his home with Trevor. Although Devin has hired some
   Merryweather protecting, it's nothing compared to the last few shootouts
   you've been through. Waste the guards with an assault rifle and approach the
   swimming pool. Devin is in the trunk, so get close enough to trigger a scene.

        CONGRATULATIONS! YOU'VE BEATEN THE MAIN STORYLINE OF THE GAME!</content>
   </chapter>
</Walkthrough>
</rss>